A Guide to the Papers of Agnes Rothery Pratt, 1935-1942
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Agnes Rothery Pratt 1935-1942
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
1366
This collection consists of 70 (ca.) items.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift on 1942 March 5.
Scope and Content Information
Collection contains galley proof and manuscript of "Family album"; manuscript of "Washington roundabout"; notes and printed materials used to research the latter; and correspondence related to both works.
Contents List
- Washington roundabout by Agnes Rothery Pratt 1942, TMs. (2 folders) (Box 1)
- Washington roundabout by Agnes 1941-1942 (Box 1)
- Washington roundabout by Agnes Rothery Pratt: Printed Material used for background 1935-1942, n.d., (2 folders) (Box 1)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt, Chapters 1-6 1942, TMs (Box 1)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt, Chapter 7 1942, TMs (Box 1)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt, Chapters 8-12 1942, TMs (Box 1)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt, Chapters 13-16 1942, TMs (Box 2)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt, Chapters 17-19 1942, TMs (Box 2)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt, Chapters 20-25 1942, TMs (Box 2)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt, Chapter 11 and miscellaneous pages 1942, TMs (Box 2)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt 1942, Galley Proof (Box 2)
- Family Album by Agnes Rothery Pratt: Correspondence 1940-1942 (Box 2)